Dasari Prabhu Teja

Enthusiast | Developer

+91 6302852884

✓ prabhuteja985@gmail.com

Rajahmundry AP, India

SUMMARY

Technology enthusiast who is highly skilled and have 1+ years of experience in both the software and hardware fields. Always eager to learn and experiment with new things. A team player who seeks out better solutions. Always ready to tackle new challenges. Have the ability to quickly learn and adapt to different circumstances.

EDUCATION

Electronics and Communication Engineering

06/2018 - Present

Aditya Engineering College - Bachelor of Technology

MPC 06/2016 - 04/2018

Tirumala Junior College - Senior Secondary

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Intern 06/2021 - 08/2021

Tech Citi Software Solutions, Bengaluru

- Created the hospital web application using angular Js as frontend in angular.
- Developed a dashboard website using angular Js and used Mongo DB to store the data
- Built patient, labs, doctor, pharmacy, reception web application in angular js.
- Built patient application to book the appointments and to view the lab results and to view the bill in web application.
- Built Doctor application to view the appointments for concern problems to diagonize for patient problems And to assign the lab test and to assign medicine prescriptions to assign the pharmacy in web application.
- Built reception to view the appointments and to collect the money and to assign the doctor and As per the concern problem and to view the medicine prescriptions and to view the lab test in web application.
- Built labs to view the lab request from doctor to test the patient and to send the lab reports to doctor and patient in web Application
- Built pharmacy to view the doctor prescription and to add, update, delete the medicines records and to send the medicine Bill to reception, patient and collect the money UPI, Cash from web application
- Built a backend for a Hospital Management portal that allow patient reports, lab reports, pharmacy bills and uses MongoDB to store the data

T-Connect Mentor

02/2021 - 02/2021

Technical Hub, Kakinada.

 Motivated 500+ students by emphasizing the need to learn diverse technologies that are currently leading the market.

Web Mentor 12/2019 - 12/2019

Technical Hub, Kakinada.

• Motivated 300+ students by highlighting the importance of Web technologies in a variety of fields and demonstrated real-world Webapplications.

PROJECTS

Credential Vault | Web Application

08/2020 - 09/2020

- Built this web app on the idea of storing credentials safely. It allows users to store their passwords safely.
- Enhanced security used encryption technologies to keep data safe and secure.
- Created this application using Flutter Framework and Firebase as Database.

Formula | Mobile Application

07/2020 - 08/2020

- Offers a wide range of formulas from many disciplines.
- Enables users to calculate them using their own data.
- Built this app using Flutter and Firebase

Smart Plug Project 04/2019 - 12/2019

The Smart Plug is an IoT-based electrical plug. It remotely monitors and controls the device connected to it.

- Precisely monitors the power consumption of a connected device.
- Created a Website and Mobile App to allow users to control and monitor devices that are linked to it.

SKILLS

Technical Skills: Python, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, IoT, AWS, Networking, Flutter, Flask, Firebase, Arduino, SQL. **Soft Skills:** Effective Communication, Team Building, Committed to Lifelong Learning.

CERTIFICATIONS

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA)	09/2021
AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner	03/2022
HTML5 - Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA)	02/2020
Python - Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA)	05/2019
IoT Fundamentals - Cisco	04/2019

EVENTS & HACKATHONS

Project Space | Technical Hub

- Built the Smart Plug device, which is powered by the Internet of Things.
- Created a website using Flask as backend and MySQL to store the data.
- Collaborated with a 3D design team to design the outer case for the Smart Plug.
- Awarded first prize, out of all 43 projects.

Tech Makeover | Technical Hub

- Built the Social Tracker based on Internet on Things. Developed this for Technical Hub at Aditya Engineering College.
- Enabled the organization to showcase its social media following.

ACHIEVEMENTS

• Won 1st prize out of 43 teams for the smart plug in the project space event organized by Technical Hub.

- Emerging Techno award for committed learning.
- Won 1st prize out of 20 teams for the smart plug in the IoT Hackathon.

WORK SAMPLES & OTHER LINKS

GitHub: github.com/tejadasari985

Website https://siloamchurchndd.nifty-cannon.13-235-157-224.plesk.page/

Website: https://siloamchurchndd.nifty-cannon.13-235-157-224.plesk.page/